

# **INFO**

# NAME

Ajay Ghimire

#### **ADDRESS**

7-9 Churchill Avenue. Strathfield, NSW 2135

#### **PHONE**

0404286785

#### **EMAIL**

LINKEDIN

**PORTFOLIO WEBSITE** 

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### LANGUAGES

- JavaScript
- Ruby
- Java (Actively Learning)
- HTML / CSS

# FRAMEWORKS / **LIBRARIES**

- React
- Redux
- Express.js
- Next.js
- Ruby on Rails

# TOOLS

- Git Source Control
- AWS (Basic)
- VS Code and Eclipse

# RELEVANT **CERTIFICATIONS**

- React + Redux
- Ruby
- Responsive Web Design

## **PROFILE**

An aspiring junior developer with a solid 4-year foundation in software development from a bachelor's degree, combined with a software engineering bootcamp, and sustained self-directed study and professional development. Honed impressive problem-solving and creative thinking skills through continuous academic projects development. Driven by a desire and an unwavering commitment to leveraging technology for social good, seeking to pursue a fulfilling career in software development.

# **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Software Engineering Transform Academy Xi

Sydney

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

#### **ACADEMIC PROJECTS**

- WITH LOVE FROM HOME
- **MEMEBOOK**
- CRYPTOMANIA
- PLAY MATES
- **MOVIE FINDER**

# Bachelor of Information Technology and Systems (BITS)

**Major: Software Development Victorian Institute of Technology** 

Sydney

Jul 2018 - Jul 2021

#### SIDE PROJECTS

- **GOALS TO SCORE**
- YOUTIFY

### RELEVENT EXPERIENCE

# Web Developer Intern, Brand Easy Australia

Campsie

Dec 2022 - Present

- Collaborated with the development team to plan, develop, test, deploy, and maintain web applications.
- Participated in code reviews and documentation and contributed to the creation of technical documentation and user manuals.
- Worked with project managers to prioritize tasks and ensure timely delivery of projects.

#### OTHER EXPERIENCES

#### **Retail Assistant, Chemist Warehouse**

Dec 2022 - Present

Brookvale

Cook, Cho Cho San

Jan 2018 - Nov 2022

Potts Point